 export const sports =  [
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "At%20which%20bridge%20does%20the%20annual%20Oxford%20and%20Cambridge%20boat%20race%20start%3F",
"correct_answer": "Putney",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Hammersmith",
"Vauxhall%20",
"Battersea"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "With%20which%20team%20did%20Michael%20Schumacher%20make%20his%20Formula%20One%20debut%20at%20the%201991%20Belgian%20Grand%20Prix%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jordan",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Benetton",
"Ferrari",
"Mercedes"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20German%20sportswear%20company%27s%20logo%20is%20the%20%27Formstripe%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Puma",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Nike",
"Adidas",
"Reebok"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20cricketing%20term%20denotes%20a%20batsman%20being%20dismissed%20with%20a%20score%20of%20zero%3F",
"correct_answer": "Duck",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Bye",
"Beamer",
"Carry"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20teams%20isn%27t%20a%20member%20of%20the%20NHL%27s%20%22Original%20Six%22%20era%3F",
"correct_answer": "Philadelphia%20Flyers",
"incorrect_answers": [
"New%20York%20Rangers",
"Toronto%20Maple%20Leafs",
"Boston%20Bruins"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20was%20the%20British%20professional%20wrestler%20Shirley%20Crabtree%20better%20known%20as%3F",
"correct_answer": "Big%20Daddy",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Giant%20Haystacks",
"Kendo%20Nagasaki",
"Masambula"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20nickname%20of%20Northampton%20town%27s%20rugby%20union%20club%3F",
"correct_answer": "Saints",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Harlequins",
"Saracens",
"Wasps"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "A%20stimpmeter%20measures%20the%20speed%20of%20a%20ball%20over%20what%20surface%3F",
"correct_answer": "Golf%20Putting%20Green",
"incorrect_answers": [
"%20Football%20Pitch",
"Cricket%20Outfield",
"Pinball%20Table"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20Formula%20One%20driver%20was%20nicknamed%20%27The%20Professor%27%3F",
"correct_answer": "Alain%20Prost",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ayrton%20Senna",
"Niki%20Lauda",
"Emerson%20Fittipaldi"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20scoring%20zones%20are%20there%20on%20a%20conventional%20dart%20board%3F",
"correct_answer": "82",
"incorrect_answers": [
"62",
"42",
"102"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20a%20game%20of%20snooker%2C%20what%20colour%20ball%20is%20worth%203%20points%3F",
"correct_answer": "Green",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Yellow",
"Brown",
"Blue"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20nation%20hosted%20the%20FIFA%20World%20Cup%20in%202006%3F",
"correct_answer": "Germany",
"incorrect_answers": [
"United%20Kingdom",
"Brazil",
"South%20Africa"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "The%20F1%20season%20of%201994%20is%20remembered%20for%20what%20tragic%20event%3F",
"correct_answer": "Death%20of%20Ayrton%20Senna%20%28San%20Marino%29",
"incorrect_answers": [
"The%20Showdown%20%28Australia%29",
"Verstappen%20on%20Fire%20%28Germany%29",
"Schumacher%27s%20Ban%20%28Britain%29"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20highest%20belt%20you%20can%20get%20in%20Taekwondo%3F",
"correct_answer": "Black",
"incorrect_answers": [
"White",
"Red",
"Green"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20country%20is%20hosting%20the%202022%20FIFA%20World%20Cup%3F",
"correct_answer": "Qatar",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Uganda",
"Vietnam",
"Bolivia"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20team%20was%20the%202015-2016%20NBA%20Champions%3F",
"correct_answer": "Cleveland%20Cavaliers",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Golden%20State%20Warriors",
"Toronto%20Raptors",
"Oklahoma%20City%20Thunders"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20team%20was%20the%202014-2015%20NBA%20Champions%3F",
"correct_answer": "Golden%20State%20Warriors",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Cleveland%20Cavaliers",
"Houston%20Rockets",
"Atlanta%20Hawks"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Josh%20Mansour%20is%20part%20of%20what%20NRL%20team%3F",
"correct_answer": "Penrith%20Panthers",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Melbourne%20Storm",
"Sydney%20Roosters",
"North%20Queensland%20Cowboys"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20car%20manufacturer%20won%20the%202016%2024%20Hours%20of%20Le%20Mans%3F",
"correct_answer": "Porsche",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Toyota",
"Audi",
"Ferrari"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20soccer%20team%20won%20the%20Copa%20Am%C3%A9rica%202015%20Championship%20%3F",
"correct_answer": "Chile",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Argentina",
"Brazil",
"Paraguay"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20soccer%20team%20won%20the%20Copa%20Am%C3%A9rica%20Centenario%202016%3F",
"correct_answer": "Chile",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Argentina",
"Brazil",
"Colombia"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20national%20team%20won%20the%202016%20edition%20of%20UEFA%20European%20Championship%3F",
"correct_answer": "Portugal",
"incorrect_answers": [
"France",
"Germany",
"England"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%202016%2C%20who%20won%20the%20Formula%201%20World%20Constructor%27s%20Championship%20for%20the%20third%20time%20in%20a%20row%3F",
"correct_answer": "Mercedes-AMG%20Petronas",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Scuderia%20Ferrari",
"McLaren%20Honda",
"Red%20Bull%20Racing%20Renault"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20oldest%20team%20in%20Major%20League%20Baseball%3F",
"correct_answer": "Atlanta%20Braves",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Chicago%20Cubs",
"Cincinnati%20Reds",
"St.%20Louis%20Cardinals"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20Formula%201%2C%20the%20Virtual%20Safety%20Car%20was%20introduced%20following%20the%20fatal%20crash%20of%20which%20driver%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jules%20Bianchi",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Ayrton%20Senna",
"Ronald%20Ratzenberger",
"Gilles%20Villeneuve"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20Grand%20Slam%20tennis%20tournaments%20occurs%20LAST%3F",
"correct_answer": "US%20Open",
"incorrect_answers": [
"French%20Open",
"Wimbledon",
"Australian%20Open"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20exact%20length%20of%20one%20non-curved%20part%20in%20Lane%201%20of%20an%20Olympic%20Track%3F",
"correct_answer": "84.39m",
"incorrect_answers": [
"100m",
"100yd",
"109.36yd"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20portuguese%20island%20is%20soccer%20player%20Cristiano%20Ronaldo%20from%3F",
"correct_answer": "Madeira",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Terceira",
"Santa%20Maria",
"Porto%20Santo"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20won%20the%20%22Champions%20League%22%20in%201999%3F",
"correct_answer": "Manchester%20United",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Barcelona",
"Bayern%20Munich",
"Liverpool"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20won%20the%202015%20College%20Football%20Playoff%20%28CFP%29%20National%20Championship%3F%20",
"correct_answer": "Ohio%20State%20Buckeyes",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Alabama%20Crimson%20Tide",
"Clemson%20Tigers",
"Wisconsin%20Badgers"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20year%20was%20hockey%20legend%20Wayne%20Gretzky%20born%3F",
"correct_answer": "1961",
"incorrect_answers": [
"1965",
"1959",
"1963"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20the%20following%20pitchers%20was%20named%20National%20League%20Rookie%20of%20the%20Year%20for%20the%202013%20season%3F",
"correct_answer": "Jose%20Fernandez",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Jacob%20deGrom",
"Shelby%20Miller",
"Matt%20Harvey"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Why%20was%20The%20Green%20Monster%20at%20Fenway%20Park%20was%20originally%20built%3F",
"correct_answer": "To%20prevent%20viewing%20games%20from%20outside%20the%20park.",
"incorrect_answers": [
"To%20make%20getting%20home%20runs%20harder.",
"To%20display%20advertisements.",
"To%20provide%20extra%20seating."
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20sport%20is%20NOT%20traditionally%20played%20during%20the%20Mongolian%20Naadam%20festival%3F",
"correct_answer": "American%20Football",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Wrestling",
"Archery",
"Horse-Racing"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20car%20manufacturer%20won%20the%202017%2024%20Hours%20of%20Le%20Mans%3F",
"correct_answer": "Porsche",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Toyota",
"Audi",
"Chevrolet"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20NBA%20player%20won%20Most%20Valuable%20Player%20for%20the%201999-2000%20season%3F",
"correct_answer": "Shaquille%20O%27Neal",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Allen%20Iverson",
"Kobe%20Bryant",
"Paul%20Pierce"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "In%20what%20sport%20does%20Fanny%20Chmelar%20compete%20for%20Germany%3F",
"correct_answer": "Skiing",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Swimming",
"Showjumping",
"Gymnastics"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "How%20many%20premier%20league%20trophies%20did%20Sir%20Alex%20Ferguson%20win%20during%20his%20time%20at%20Manchester%20United%3F",
"correct_answer": "13",
"incorrect_answers": [
"11",
"20",
"22"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20is%20Manchester%20United%27s%20top%20premier%20league%20goal%20scorer%3F",
"correct_answer": "Wayne%20Rooney",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sir%20Bobby%20Charlton",
"Ryan%20Giggs",
"David%20Beckham"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20professional%20wrestler%20fell%20from%20the%20rafters%20to%20his%20death%20during%20a%20live%20Pay-Per-View%20event%20in%201999%3F",
"correct_answer": "Owen%20Hart",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Chris%20Benoit",
"Lex%20Luger",
"Al%20Snow"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20was%20the%20topscorer%20for%20England%20national%20football%20team%3F",
"correct_answer": "Wayne%20Rooney",
"incorrect_answers": [
"David%20Beckham",
"Steven%20Gerrard",
"Michael%20Owen"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20Formula%201%20driver%20switched%20teams%20in%20the%20middle%20of%20the%202017%20season%3F",
"correct_answer": "Carlos%20Sainz%20Jr.",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Daniil%20Kvyat",
"Jolyon%20Palmer",
"Rio%20Haryanto"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20Tiger%20Woods%27%20all-time%20best%20career%20golf-score%3F",
"correct_answer": "61",
"incorrect_answers": [
"65",
"63",
"67"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20won%20the%202011%20Stanley%20Cup%3F",
"correct_answer": "Boston%20Bruins",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Montreal%20Canadiens",
"New%20York%20Rangers",
"Toronto%20Maple%20Leafs"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20AHL%20affiliate%20of%20the%20Toronto%20Maple%20Leafs%3F",
"correct_answer": "Toronto%20Marlies",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Toronto%20Rock",
"Toronto%20Argonauts",
"Toronto%20Wolfpack"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "What%20country%20hosted%20the%202014%20Winter%20Olympics%3F",
"correct_answer": "Russia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Canada",
"United%20States",
"Germany"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20basketball%20team%20has%20attended%20the%20most%20NBA%20grand%20finals%3F",
"correct_answer": "Los%20Angeles%20Lakers",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Boston%20Celtics",
"Philadelphia%2076ers",
"Golden%20State%20Warriors"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20country%20did%20Kabaddi%2C%20a%20contact%20sport%20involving%20tackling%2C%20originate%20from%3F",
"correct_answer": "India",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Australia",
"Turkey",
"Cambodia"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Which%20of%20these%20countries%27%20national%20teams%20qualified%20for%20the%202018%20FIFA%20World%20Cup%20in%20Russia%3F",
"correct_answer": "Tunisia",
"incorrect_answers": [
"United%20States%20of%20America",
"Italy",
"Netherlands"
]
},
{
"category": "Sports",
"type": "multiple",
"difficulty": "medium",
"question": "Who%20won%20the%202018%20Monaco%20Grand%20Prix%3F",
"correct_answer": "Daniel%20Ricciardo",
"incorrect_answers": [
"Sebastian%20Vettel",
"Kimi%20Raikkonen",
"Lewis%20Hamilton"
]
}
]